export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the largest coal producer in Asia?",
    answer1: "Chine",
    answer2: "India",
    answer3: "Turkey",
    correctAnswer: "China",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the largest oil producer in Asia?",
    answer1: "Japan",
    answer2: "North Korea",
    answer3: "Saudi Arabia",
    correctAnswer: "Saudi Arabia",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the most spoken language in Asia?",
    answer1: "Turkish",
    answer2: "Japanese",
    answer3: "Mandarin Chinese",
    correctAnswer: "Mandarin Chinese",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "In which country is the Galata Bridge which connects Europe to Asia?",
    answer1: "Russia",
    answer2: "Turkey",
    answer3: "Greece",
    correctAnswer: "Turkey",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is a city state?",
    answer1: "Taiwan",
    answer2: "Vietnam",
    answer3: "Singapore",
    correctAnswer: "Singapore",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Taipei is the capital city of which country?",
    answer1: "Taiwan",
    answer2: "Thailand",
    answer3: "Vietnam",
    correctAnswer: "Taiwan",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Kim Jong-un is the leader of which country?",
    answer1: "Thailand",
    answer2: "South Korea",
    answer3: "North Korea",
    correctAnswer: "North Korea",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Vientiane is the capital of which country?",
    answer1: "Yemen",
    answer2: "Laos",
    answer3: "Lebanon",
    correctAnswer: "Laos",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Amman is which country's capital city?",
    answer1: "Jordan",
    answer2: "Israel",
    answer3: "Myanmar",
    correctAnswer: "Jordan",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which is the predominant color on the national flag of Turkmenistan?",
    answer1: "White",
    answer2: "Blue",
    answer3: "Green",
    correctAnswer: "Green",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "A mapping study determined in 2009 that the Great Wall of China was how long?",
    answer1: "5250 miles",
    answer2: "5500 miles",
    answer3: "5750 miles",
    correctAnswer: "5500 miles",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Siam was the former name of which country?",
    answer1: "Thailand",
    answer2: "The Philippines",
    answer3: "Taiwan",
    correctAnswer: "Thailand",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "In which country is the port of Latakia?",
    answer1: "Yemen",
    answer2: "Lebanon",
    answer3: "Syria",
    correctAnswer: "Syria",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Which of the following is considered an Asian country?",
    answer1: "Lithuania",
    answer2: "Burundi",
    answer3: "Uzbekistan",
    correctAnswer: "Uzbekistan",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      "Which is the predominant color on the national flag of Pakistan?",
    answer1: "Black",
    answer2: "Red",
    answer3: "Green",
    correctAnswer: "Green",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "What is the largest cinema industry in Asia?",
    answer1: "Bollywood",
    answer2: "Hollywood",
    answer3: "Yesilcam",
    correctAnswer: "Bollywood",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "What is the longest river in Asia?",
    answer1: "Yangtze River",
    answer2: "Spain",
    answer3: "Andorra",
    correctAnswer: "Yangtze River",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "What is the capital of South Korea?",
    answer1: "Seoul",
    answer2: "France",
    answer3: "Netherlands",
    correctAnswer: "Seoul",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What is the capital of India?",
    answer1: "The Vltava River",
    answer2: "The Po River",
    answer3: "New Delhi",
    correctAnswer: "The Vltava River",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "What is the highest mountain in Asia?  ",
    answer1: "France",
    answer2: "Mount Everest",
    answer3: "Switzerland",
    correctAnswer: "Mount Everest",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "What is the largest Muslim country in Asia?",
    answer1: "Indonesia",
    answer2: "Mongolia",
    answer3: "Russia",
    correctAnswer: "Indonesia",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "What is the largest desert in Asia?",
    answer1: "Gobi Desert",
    answer2: "Moscow",
    answer3: "Minsk",
    correctAnswer: "Minsk",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "What is western Asia's longest river?",
    answer1: "Tigris",
    answer2: "Euphrates",
    answer3: "Kurobe",
    correctAnswer: "Euphrates",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "What is the capital of Afghanistan?",
    answer1: "Kabul",
    answer2: "Teheran",
    answer3: "Baghdad",
    correctAnswer: "Kabul",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Which country is the largest exporter of tea in the world?",
    answer1: "Turkey",
    answer2: "China",
    answer3: "Srilanka",
    correctAnswer: "China",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question:
      "What is the name of the river that flows through Beijing, China?",
    answer1: "Sweden",
    answer2: "Hungary",
    answer3: "Yongding River",
    correctAnswer: "Yongding River",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question:
      "What is the name of the world's largest flower, which is found in Southeast Asia?",
    answer1: "euro",
    answer2: "Rafflesia",
    answer3: "lira",
    correctAnswer: "Rafflesia",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question:
      "Which country is the birthplace of the famous philosopher Confucius?",
    answer1: "china",
    answer2: "South Korea",
    answer3: "Japan",
    correctAnswer: "China",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "Which country is home to the largest river island in the world?",
    answer1: "India",
    answer2: "China",
    answer3: "Phippines",
    correctAnswer: "",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "The ringgit is the currency of which Asian country?",
    answer1: "Sri Lanka",
    answer2: "Vietnam",
    answer3: "Malaysia",
    correctAnswer: "Malaysia",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question:
      "The art of folding objects out of paper to create two-dimensional and three-dimensional subjects is called:",
    answer1: "calligraphy",
    answer2: "origami",
    answer3: "decoupage",
    correctAnswer: "origami",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question:
      "Which volcano in Japan last erupted in 1707 but is still classified as active by geologists?",
    answer1: "Mount Rinjani",
    answer2: "Taal Volcano",
    answer3: "Mount Fuji",
    correctAnswer: "Mount Fuji",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "Which mountain pass connects Kābul with Peshāwar?",
    answer1: "Khyber Pass",
    answer2: "Shipki La",
    answer3: "Diphu Pass",
    correctAnswer: "Khyber Pass",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: "Tsai Ing-wen was the first female president of which country?",
    answer1: "Cambodia",
    answer2: "Taiwan",
    answer3: "Japan",
    correctAnswer: "Taiwan",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "What is the main color of China’s flag?",
    answer1: "blue",
    answer2: "green",
    answer3: "red",
    correctAnswer: "red",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "Which of these cities lies on the Saigon River?",
    answer1: "Hong Kong",
    answer2: "Hanoi",
    answer3: "Ho Chi Minh City",
    correctAnswer: "Ho Chi Minh City",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "What is the capital of Bangladesh?",
    answer1: "Dhaka",
    answer2: "Accra",
    answer3: "Aden",
    correctAnswer: "Dhaka",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: "What is the oldest existing freshwater lake on Earth?",
    answer1: "Lake Superior",
    answer2: "Lake Victoria",
    answer3: "Lake Baikal",
    correctAnswer: "Lake Baikal",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "Which road links Myanmar with China?",
    answer1: "Burma Road",
    answer2: "Karakoram Highway",
    answer3: "Appian Way",
    correctAnswer: "Burma Road",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question:
      "Which of following bodies of water separates Asia from the African continent?",
    answer1: "Arabian Sea",
    answer2: "Suez Canal",
    answer3: "Red Sea",
    correctAnswer: "Suez Canal",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    question: "In what ocean does Indonesia lie?",
    answer1: "Southern",
    answer2: "Arctic",
    answer3: "Pacific",
    correctAnswer: "Pacific",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: "In which country is the Kamchatka Peninsula situated?",
    answer1: "Russia",
    answer2: "Turkey",
    answer3: "Mongolia",
    correctAnswer: "Russia",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: "What is the longest river in Southeast Asia?",
    answer1: "Chao Phraya River",
    answer2: "Mekong River",
    answer3: "Salween River",
    correctAnswer: "Mekong River",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question: "What country does the Mekong River not flow through?",
    answer1: "Laos",
    answer2: "Mongolia",
    answer3: "China",
    correctAnswer: "Mongolia",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question: "Which ancient trade route linked the Western world with Asia?",
    answer1: "Silk Road",
    answer2: "Via Maris",
    answer3: "Oregon Trail",
    correctAnswer: "Silk Road",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question: "In which city were the first Asian Games held?",
    answer1: "New Delhi",
    answer2: "Jakarta",
    answer3: "Seoul",
    correctAnswer: "New Delhi",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question:
      "Which waterway connects the Andaman Sea and the South China Sea?",
    answer1: "Cook Strait",
    answer2: "Bering Strait",
    answer3: "Strait of Malacca",
    correctAnswer: "Strait of Malacca",
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 48,
    question: "What is the largest port city in South Korea?",
    answer1: "Pusan",
    answer2: "Seoul",
    answer3: "Ulsan",
    correctAnswer: "Pusan",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "Which city hosted the 1964 Olympic Games?",
    answer1: "Barcelona",
    answer2: "Tokyo",
    answer3: "Rome",
    correctAnswer: "Tokyo",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: "What is the capital city of Turkey?",
    answer1: "Istanbul",
    answer2: "Antalya",
    answer3: "Ankara",
    correctAnswer: "Ankara",
    isAnswered: false,
  },
];
